[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What molecule has the formula O3?", "correct_answer": "Ozone", "incorrect_answers": ["Tritium", "Deuterium", "Peroxide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did all Indian tribes of North America eat turkeys or consider them to be edible?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aladdins father is the king of thieves.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mall in this city has its own 400-meter ski slope.", "correct_answer": "Dubai", "incorrect_answers": ["Denver", "Oslo", "Edmonton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the fine for shooting a Thylacine?", "correct_answer": "$5,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$10,000", "$1,000", "$3,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This European river originates in Germany and empties in the Black Sea via a delta.", "correct_answer": "The Danube", "incorrect_answers": ["The Volga", "The Rhine", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What two colors are mixed together to get orange?", "correct_answer": "Red and yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow and green", "Blue and red", "White and blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Control of the Ganges River, sacred to some people, has been much disputed between which two nations?", "correct_answer": "India and Bangladesh", "incorrect_answers": ["India and Myanmar", "India and Pakistan", "India and China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie released in 2007 was about a group of people trapped in an Alaskan town with blood thirsty vampires.", "correct_answer": "30 Days of Night", "incorrect_answers": ["Halloween", "28 Days Later", "Vampires"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Socrates believed that wrongdoing stems only from this phenomenon.", "correct_answer": "Ignorance", "incorrect_answers": ["Egoism", "Frustration", "Hopelessness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During which lunar phase is the moon least visible?", "correct_answer": "Waxing Crescent", "incorrect_answers": ["First Quarter", "Full Moon", "Waxing Gibbous"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Several westerns have been made about this famous family of brothers that rode into history on both sides of the law.", "correct_answer": "Earp", "incorrect_answers": ["James", "Dalton", "Kidd"]}]